Grand Canyon
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Grand Canyon
2.1.1.1.9
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1183
- Grand Canyon, 2.1.1.1.9
  - Hopi house opposite El Tovar, 1911; 1; 15000; 55; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - El Tovar Hotel, showing position of edge of canyon, 1911; 2; 15002; 59; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Dead trees on the edge of the Grand Canyon, 1911; 3; 15005; 81; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Hopi forests, 1911; 4; 15006; 95; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Trees showing mistletoe parasites, 1911; 5; 15007; 35; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Dwarf forests at Grand Canyon, 1911; 6; 15008; 87; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Indian paint brush, 1911; 7; 15009; 279; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Rabbit foot, 1911; 8; 15010; 273; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Yucca plant, 1911; 9; 15011; 272; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Looking toward Bright Angel Trail, 1911; 10; 15012; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Bottom of Bright Angel Trail, 1911; 11; 15013; 69; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Grand Canyon from Datle Lands[?] in plateau, 1911; 12; 15016; 92; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Balk water of Colorado River, 1911; 13; 15018; 138; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Bright Angel Trail, Yucca, 1911; 14; 15019; 139; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Bright Angel Trail from Grandeur or El Tovar Point, 1911; 15; 15020; 148; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Looking toward "steamboat", 1911; 16; 15021; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Cheops, Buddha and Manu from Grandeur of El Tovar point, 1911; 17; 15022; 57; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Looking north from Grand View Point, 1911; 18; 15023; 114; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - From Grand View Point toward Wotan's Throne, 1911; 19; 15025; 27; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Grand Canyon taken from near El Tovar Hotel, 1911; 20; 15026; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Canyon from El Tovar Hotel, 1911 July; 21; 15027; 43; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Looking west from Hopi Point, 1911; 22; 15028; 42; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Grand Canyon west from Maricopa Point, 1911; 23; 15029; 68; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Looking west from Maricopa Point, 1911; 24; 15030; 52; 5x7 (Box 1183)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party on Bright Angel Trail, 1911; 25; 15031; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Indian chief, Hopi house, 1911; 26; 15032; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Frank R. Roberson and an Indian baby, 1911; 27; 15033; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Indian mud house, 1911; 28; 15034; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Indian family, 1911; 29; 15035; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Indian woman and baby, 1911; 30; 15036; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Indian women and children, 1911; 31; 15037; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Indian children, 1911; 32; 15038; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Indian woman and baby, 1911; 33; 15039; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Group of Indians, 1911; 34; 15040; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Indian men and women, 1911; 35; 15041; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Pack mules on Bright Angel Trail, 1911; 36; 15042; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Looking into the canyon from the Bright Angel Trail, 1911; 37; 15043; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Photographic outfit packed on mule, Frank R. Roberson standing by mule, 1911; 38; 15044; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - The end of the Bright Angel Trail at the Colorado River, 1911; 39; 15045; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - People watching the sunset at Hopi Point, 1911; 40; 15046; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Roberson party (Dodmun[?]) on Bright Angel trail, 1911; 41; 15047; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - At bottom of Bright Angel Trail, 1911; 42; 15048; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Grand View Trail, 1911; 43; 15049; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Part of old Grand View Trail, 1911; 44; 15050; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Side wall of canyon along Bright Angel Trail, 1911; 45; 15051; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Side wall of canyon to show color, 1911; 46; 15052; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Detail of Grand Canyon formation, 1911; 47; 15053; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Grand Canyon formation at Grand View Point, 1911; 48; 15054; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - North wall of canyon, 1911; 49; 15055; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Zoroaster, 1911; 50; 15056; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  - Grand View Point, 1911; 51; 15057; 4x5 (Box 1183)
  Box 1184
- Grand Canyon, 2.1.1.1.9
  - Looking toward Cheops, 1911; 1; 15058; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Looking toward Zoroaster, 1911; 2; 15059; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Looking toward Shiva and Isis, 1911; 3; 15060; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Wagon on the Grand Canyon roads, 1911; 4; 15061; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Frank R. Roberson on Hopi Point, 1911; 5; 15063; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Sunset from Hopi Point, 1911; 6; 15064; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Sunset from Hopi Point, looking northwest, 1911; 7; 15065; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Sunset from Hopi Point, looking west, 1911; 8; 15066; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Sunset at Hopi Point, looking northwest, 1911; 9; 15067; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Sunset at Hopi Point, looking down the canyon, 1911; 10; 15068; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - The sun on the brink of the canyon, 1911; 11; 15069; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Sunset at Hopi Point, 1911; 12; 15070; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Mountain mahogany, 1911; 13; 15071; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - "Horsefly lilac", lupine, 1911; 14; 15073; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Miss Heyder and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson on the edge of the Grand Canyon, 1911; 15; 15074; 4x5 (Box 1184)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson at El Tovar Point, 1911; 16; 15075; 4x5 (Box 1184)